paidforresearch.com 2018-06-09

# Our Privacy Policy : Get Paid to Take Surveys : Marketing Survey : Online Surveys for Money : PaidForResearch.com

This privacy statement covers the site at [http://www.paidforresearch.com](http://www.paidforresearch.com/onlinesurvey/maincsp.php). The site is an internet web property of Paid for research  Paid for research wants to demonstrate its commitment to its users' privacy so it invites public comment about this policy.  The statement explains the following:  
What personally identifiable information Paid for research collects.  
How Paid for research will notify users if it begins collecting more information.  
How users can correct any inaccuracies in their information.   
Third parties and how we share data on limited basis.    
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact   
Or send email to [privacycomments@paidforresearch.com](mailto:privacycomments@paidforresearch.com)

**_Information Collection_  
**  
To set up your free membership, you will need to provide certain contact information. The requested information may include any combination of data such as your name, mailing, address, e-mail address, phone number, amongst other contact information requirements. This registration info is required if you wish to enroll on the Web Site. The registration form information requests may change from time to time. We may append additional data we obtain from our other owned web sites or third parties to your enrollment information for analysis and marketing purposes. This information will also allow us to provide better, more relevant offers to you.   
Paid for research collects information from users at specific places on its web site such as standard web sites use log files.  This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  None of this information is linked to personally identifiable information.  This web site automatically records the user's IP address to help diagnose problems with the server, and to administer the web site. IP address information is also used to track the popularity of research programs. The web server uses a cookie file to recognize users and remember certain preferences. The cookie is updated by the web server with each visit to the site.  
**_  
Membership_** Becoming a member of the site requires that the user provide a real name and email address. Access to the member program requires name, email, gender, address, phone number.  Other sites may require  additional information before allowing participation in a research program, special offers, or surveys. Paid for research is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web site or third party links found on site.   
Information about client accounts is kept in a database available only to individuals authorized by Paid for research. Paid for research will only share your email address with our exclusive email partner, for the purpose of sending relevant, daily third party promotional emails. 

**_Advertisements and Data Sharing_**  
**_  
Legal Disclaimer_** Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law where we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us.    
Paid for research depends on advertisements to offer its free services. We make every effort to get you the best offers and user experience on our site.  We may always use and share with others your personal information for managing your account and to enable us to generally respond to you.  Paid for research may also use personal information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of itself and its trusted affiliates and subsidiaries. Paid for research may disclose personal information to third party agents and independent contractors that help us conduct our marketing and survey efforts. Further, paid for research may disclose personal information to other companies in connection with marketing efforts including but not limited to direct marketing, which may have no relationship to paid for research. We may partner with other parties to provide specific services. It may be necessary to share names, or other contact information with a third party(ies) to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.  By registering you grant to us the right, subject to applicable state and federal law:  (1) to share your registration information such as name, email, phone , mailing address with third party advertisers and marketers; to use  your registration Information in order to send you information about products and/or services that we, and/or our third party advertisers and marketers, think may be of  interest to you, or products that we or our third party advertisers and marketers offer and/or other information that we believe that you may find valuable. If, at any time, you  do not wish to receive such information, you may chose to unsubscribe as detailed below.  We reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute any and all  contact information with/to any third-party for any and all uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law.  These third-parties may include, but shall not be limited to, providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation, and e-mail marketing.  We may also use your registration info for any program related purpose, and/or marketing and survey purpose, on our own behalf and on behalf of our affiliates and subsidiaries. We may disclose registration info to third-party agents and independent contractors that help us operate the program.  You agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the site. By submitting your e-mail address at the Site, you agree to  receive e-mail marketing from us and our third party advertisers and marketers.  We, and our third party advertisers and marketers, may maintain separate e-mail lists for different purposes. If you wish to end your e-mail subscription to a particular list, you must follow the instructions contained in each e-mail correspondence that you receive from us, the applicable third party advertiser or marketer, to unsubscribe from that particular list. To unsubscribe from all of our e-mail lists, please follow the instructions set forth in the section below.  We only send e-mail marketing to individuals that have agreed to receive e-mail from us and to individuals that have otherwise agreed, on third party websites, to receive e-mail marketing from companies such as us. We do not send unsolicited commercial e-mail. As a result, certain statutes requiring particular formatting for unsolicited commercial e-mail may not be applicable to the commercial e-mail that is sent by us. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not send you any e-mail marketing, or allow any third party to send you e-mail marketing, from which you cannot unsubscribe.  
By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the requirements of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time (“CAN-SPAM”) or any other applicable state or federal law, rule or regulation. In addition, you agree that by submitting your registration info at the Site, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended   
Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR §310 et seq. (the “ATSR”). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR. Moreover, by registering with, making a purchase or requesting information from, a third-party advertiser at or through the Site, such action shall constitute a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application with the respective third-party advertiser for purposes of CAN-SPAM and the ATSR and, as such, you may be contacted via e-mail, direct mail and/or telephone by such third-party advertiser in accordance with CAN-SPAM and the ATSR.

  Through the paid for research, we may provide links to third-party web sites, such as those of our advertisers. Each of these web sites have separate privacy and data-collection practices, which may differ from paid for research, and we are not responsible for the actions or practices of these third parties, nor for the content on these web sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these web sites before providing your personally identifiable information

  We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site or within our email newsletters. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect user information (e.g., hashed, de-identified, data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at http://www.aboutads.info/choices   
**_  
Children’s online privacy protection ACT_** The Site is not intended for use by children and anyone who provides a date of birth under the age of 13 will be prohibited from accessing the Site. Paid for research encourages parents and guardians to be familiar with the web sites that their children visit. The Federal Trade Commission ("FTC") regulates the means by which web site operators collect and use personal information from children under 13, pursuant to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (the "Act").  
**_  
Business Transitions_**

In the event Paid for research goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.  Paid for research will notify users, via the procedure indicated below, prior to any change in this Privacy Statement as a result of a change in ownership or control of users' personal information.   
**_  
Security_**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
**_  
Notification of Changes_**

Paid for research invites comment on its privacy policy and it reserves the right to make changes to this policy as necessary. Paid for research will post proposed changes to this privacy statement on a separate page at <http://www.paidforresearch.com/updates.html> so that users are always aware of what information is collected and under what circumstances, if any, it gets disclosed.  Paid for research will always use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.     
**_  
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information_**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done  by emailing our Customer Support at [support@paidforresearch.com](mailto:support@paidforresearch.com). Or you may contact us by postal mail at the contact information listed below.  
We may maintain separate e-mail lists for different purposes. If e-mail recipients wish to end their e-mail subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each e-mail message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all of our e-mail lists, a person must e-mail, or send a written request to our Customer Service Manager at the below address:

To opt-out of having your information shared with third-parties, please Click Here. Please be advised, however, that when you select this opt-out option, we will still share  
your information with third parties, as necessary, in order to operate the Program and/or process any transaction that you entered into by and through the Site for as long as you are a Member. We will promptly update our records upon receiving your clear instructions to opt-out, but it may take up to ten (10) days for the change to be fully effective.  If you later indicate that you want to receive emails from us and/or our third party advertisers and marketers after such date, then that opt-in statement will supersede any earlier opt-out request. If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third-party for marketing purposes, please mail here.

 ** _Contact Information_**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
Paid for research  
530 Lawrence Expwy. P.O. Box #380

Copyright Paid for research. All rights reserved.
